<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.ruqola.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Ruqola</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxRuqolaxx</name>
  <summary>Rocket Chat Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Client de xat del Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Klient pro Rocket Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Rocket-Chat-Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Rocket Chat Client</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Cliente para Rocket.Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Rocket Chati klient</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Rocket-keskusteluasiakas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Client de discussion Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Klien Chat Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Client Rocket Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Client van Rocket Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Klient rozmowy Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Cliente de Rocket Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Cliente Rocket Chat</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">Chatovací klient Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Rocket Chat klient</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Клієнт спілкування Rocket</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxRocket Chat Clientxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
       Ruqola is a Rocket Chat client based on QML.
       Connection is activated directly when you launch Ruqola.
       
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Ruqola és un client de xat del Rocket basat en el QML. La connexió s'activa directament en llançar el Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Ruqola je klient pro Rocket Chat založený na QML. Spojení je aktivováno přímo při spuštění aplikace Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Ruqola ist ein Rocket-Chat-Client auf der Basis von QML. Die Verbindung wird sofort aktiviert, wenn Sie Ruqola starten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Ruqola is a Rocket Chat client based on QML. Connection is activated directly when you launch Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Ruqola es un cliente para Rocket.Chat basado en QML. La conexión se activa directamente cuando se inicia Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Ruqola on QML-i peale ehitatud Rocket Chati klient. Ühendus aktiveeritakse kohe Ruqola käivitamisel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ruqola on QML:ään pohjautuva Rocket-keskusteluasiakas. Yhteys aktivoituu heti käynnistettyäsi Ruqolan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Ruqola est un client de discussion Rocket basé sur QML. La connexion est activée immédiatement dès que vous lancez Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Ruqola adalah sebuah klien Chat Rocket pada QML. Koneksi telah diaktifkan langsung ketika kamu meluncurkan Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ruqola è un client Rocket Chat basato su QML. La connessione viene attivata direttamente quando avvii Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Ruqola is een client van Rocket Chat gebaseerd op QML. Verbinden wordt direct geactiveerd wanneer u Ruqola start.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Ruqola jest klientem rozmowy Rocket opartym na QML. Połączenie jest nawiązywane bezpośrednio po uruchomieniu Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Ruqola é um cliente de Rocket Chat baseado em QML. A ligação fica activada directamente quando invocar o Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Ruqola é um cliente Rocket Chat baseado em QML. A conexão é ativada diretamente ao executar o Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Ruqola je chatovací klient Rocket založený na QML. Pripojenie sa aktivuje priamo pri spustení Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ruqola är en Rocket Chat klient baserad på QML. Anslutningen aktiveras direkt när Ruqola startas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ruqola — клієнт спілкування у мережі Rocket, заснований на технологіях QML. З'єднання активується безпосередньо, коли ви запускаєте Ruqola.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxRuqola is a Rocket Chat client based on QML. Connection is activated directly when you launch Ruqola.xx</p>
  </description>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ruqola</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ruqola</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
